Guide to the JDub Records Archive 2001-2011 MSS.330
Fales Library and Special Collections
JDub Records Archive
2001-2011
Fales Library and Special Collections
JDub Records
MSS.330
20 Linear Feet
The JDub Records Archive consists of materials compiled and collected by the JDub Records, a not-for-profit organization that forges vibrant connections to Judaism through music, media and cultural events. These archive documents the running of the office, the selection of and work with artists, planning of events, and other functions of JDub Records, and comprises press materials, adminstrative and financial records, and audiovisual elements.
Historical note
JDub is a not-for-profit organization that forges vibrant connections to Judaism through music, media and cultural events. Founded in December 2002 by two NYU students, Ben Hesse and Aaron Bisman, JDub has grown into an internationally recognized brand and has introduced proud Jewish voices squarely into mainstream culture, offering young adults opportunities to connect with their Judaism in the secular world in which they live. In its start-up phase, JDub focused on developing a small cadre of artists, including Matisyahu, SoCalled, and Balkan Beat Box, and introducing its unique programming to its target audience, primarily through events in New York City, festivals such as Bonnaroo, national CD releases, and via national media outlets such as MTV and The New York Times. Since that time, JDub's artist roster has grown to 20, spanning Israeli hip hop, Biblical indie-rock, Yiddish Punk, Cantorial Afrobeat, Sephardic rock, and Jewish Kids music, and it runs the popular website Jewcy.com. The organization has executed marketing campaigns and produced events for Random House, New Israel Fund, Nextbook, and others. - JDub Records, 2009, Retreived from JDub.org
Conditions Governing Access
Repository permission is required for access. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Scope and Content
The JDub Records Archive contains the papers, media, objects, and other records kept by JDub Records. This includes press about the company and the artists they represented, records pertaining to the upkeep of the company, media produced by and submitted to JDub, contracts with artists and venues, and ephemera related to JDub and their artists.
Arrangement
The JDub Records Archive is arranged in eight series:
Missing Title
Series I: Press
Series II: Promotion and Events
Series III: Administrative Materials
Series IV: Financial Material
Series V: Commercial Media
Series VI: Original Media
Series VII: Objects
Series VIII: Digital Data Storage
All series are arranged alphabetically.
Music business |z New York; Hebrew language |x Music; Jews |x Music |y 20th century; Jews |x Music |y 21st century; Music |x Jewish influences |x History and criticism; JDub Records; Matisyahu; Harris, Jacob; Hesse, Ben; Bisman, Aaron; Socalled; DeLeon (Musical group); Balkan Beat Box (Musical group); Sway Machinery (Musical group); LeeVees (Musical group); Soulico (Musical group); Golem (Musical group); Gangsta Rabbi; Wailing Wall (Musical group)
- Series I: Press
  Scope and Content
  This series contains press coverage, advertisements, interviews, and reviews of JDub and the artists represented by JDub, through newspapers, magazines, and online sources.
  - Balkan Beat Box, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Balkan Beat Box, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Balkan Beat Box (Global Rhythm Magazine), 2006 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Balkan Beat Box, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Balkan Beat Box, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Balkan Beat Box, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Balkan Beat Box, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ben Blutstein and Marla Bennett Memorial Concert press, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Clare Burson, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - DeLeon, 2008-2011 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "End of the Jews" - book press, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Gangsta Rabbi (Steve Lieberman), 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - General press, 2004-2009 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Girls in Trouble, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Golem, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Golem, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Golem, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Golem - Global Rhythm Magazine, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Golem - Musebox report, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Golem, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Golem, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Golem - press package, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - JDub press, 2002-2004 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - JDub press, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - JDub press, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - JDub press, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - JDub press, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - JDub press - Flaunt Magazine, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - JDub press kits, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - JDub press kits, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Jewish Hip-Hop articles, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Jewltide, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - LeeVees, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Matisyahu, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Matisyahu - magazines, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Matisyahu - press kit, Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Matisyahu - Shore Fire press, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Sagol 59, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Michael Showalter, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - So-Called, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - So-Called, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - So-Called, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - So-Called - press package, Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Songs from the Garden of Eden - record, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Soulico, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - The Sway Machinery, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - The Unity Sessions II - press release, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Wailing Wall - collages, Undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - "Jewish Standard" - Matisyahu article [flat box], 2005 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Shavua Israeli (Israeli Week) - Matisyahu article [flat box], 2005 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - The Village Voice - Matisyahu article [flat box], 2005 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Series II: Promotion and Events
  This series contains posters, flyers, cards, and advertisements of performances by JDub artists and JDub sponsored events.
  - American Shmidol Karaoke Showdown - tickets, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Balkan Beat Box - cards and flyers, Undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Balkan Beat Box - photos, Undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - BAM - Beyond Fiddler - program for Jewish Heritage Month, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Band / Set List - "Hidden Melodies Revealed" Rosh HaShana Celebration, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Ben Blutstein and Marla Bennett Memorial Concert, Israel - photos, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Ben Blutstein and Marla Bennett Memorial Concert - and mixed - photos, Undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Ben. flyer, Undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Birthright Israel - Livnot program - cards, Undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Celebrate Brooklyn! - cards and flyers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Clare Burson - cards and flyers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Dawn 2010 - Shavout party - cards (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - DeLeon - cards and flyers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Downtown Seder Passover Haggadah, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Festival of Strikes - cards, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Girls in Trouble - cards and flyers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Golem - cards and flyers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Hanukkah Party photos, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hillel's five-year plan for the USA, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - The Hip-Hop Seder (So-Called) - cards and flyers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Holiday cards, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Israel in the Age of Eminem: a Creative Brief for Israel Messaging, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - JDub - cards and flyers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - JDub - donation mailers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - JDub - flyer originals, Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Jewcy - cards and flyers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Jewltide party - cards and flyers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Jewltide photos, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Jewltide posters, Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - The LeeVees - cards and flyers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - The Macaroons - cards and flyers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - The Macaroons - coloring pictures, Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Adam Mansback - book promo card, Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Matisyahu - cards and flyers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Matisyahu - Israel concert - cards and backstage pass, Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Matisyahu - photos, contact sheets, Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Michael Showalter - cards and flyers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Milk and Honey - cards and flyers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Museum of Jewish Heritage - events flyer, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Rooftop Roots - cards and flyers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Sagol 59 - cards and flyers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Shotnez - cards and flyers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Six Points fellowship - brochure, Undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Slivovitz and Soul - cards and flyers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - So-Called - cards and flyers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Soulico - cards and flyers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - The Sway Machinery, Undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Tomer Yosef - cards and flyers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - TransLETTERS - Victoria Hanna - flyers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - The Wailing Wall presents: Hospital Blossoms, The Book, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - "Matisyahu: Live at Stubb's" album poster [flat box], Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Series III: Administrative Material
  This series contains contracts, meeting notes, correspondence, and any other material related to the day to day running of JDub Records.
  - The 8 - contracts, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - The 8 - JDub / Birthright Israel agreement, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - The 8 - show at Crocodile Cafe, Seattle, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - The 8 - show at The Independent, San Francisco, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - The 8 - show at TT the Bears, Boston, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - The 8 - show at Webster Hall, New York City, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Administrative papers - mixed, Undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Alternative record sales proposal, Undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - American Schmidol concert, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - ASCAP brochure, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Balkan Beat Box - Hannukah concert at Exhoplexx, L.A., 2007 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Bikkurim Residency paperwork, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Board agendas and notes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Board development, Undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Board of Directors - meeting notes, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Board meeting notes, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Bylaws of JDub Music Inc. - draft, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Celebrate Brooklyn - sponsor contracts, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - The Center for Leadership Initiatives - brochure, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Charles and Lynn Schusterman Family Foundation - 20 year anniversary publication, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Cleveland Partnership concept papers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Compilation licensing agreements (blank), Undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Consignment CD sales in Cafes - Adam Salof, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - "The Continuity of Discontinuity..." includes section about JDub, Undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Copyright information, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Demo deal, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - "End of the Jews" - book promotion paperwork, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Event related invoices, contracts, etc..., Undated (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Event related invoices, contracts, etc..., Undated (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Fifth anniversary event contracts, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Fine Gold Licensing agreement, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Future events, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Grand Performances (Slivovitz and Soul), 2008 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Haale Gafori - Jewltide contract, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Hadag Nachash proposal, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Hannukah Worldwide - Cleveland, L.A., Sanfrancisco, Boston, DC., 2008 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Hannukah Worldwide - Philly, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - "Holy Land Hardball" music license for film, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - ID Stickers - for artists visiting JDub office, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - JDub - abstract, Undated (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - JDub - bookings, financials, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - JDub - business plan, Undated (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - JDub - contracts, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - "JDub is..." description, Undated (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - JDub - presentation materials, Undated (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - JDub press lists, Undated (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - JDub - projects, Undated (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - JDub - strategic plan, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - JDub - strategic plan, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - JESNA - 30th Anniversary program - music provided by JDub, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Jewcy - absorption into JDub paperwork, c. 2009 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Jewcy - absorption papers and legal issues, c. 2009 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - "The Jewface Sessions" proposal (CD), Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Jewltide - agreements, 2003, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Jewltide - Boston, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Jewltide - Brooklyn, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Jewltide materials, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Joro-Boro performance contracts, 2008-2010 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Joshua Venture: Consultant and Coach, information guide, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - "Just for a Day" - community service and performance event, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - "King without a Crown" remix contract, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - "Legwork, Framework, Artwork: Engaging the next generation of Jews", 2008 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Licensing agreements, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Lilah-Birthright Israel - event series proposal, Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Matisyahu - attorney / client work product with Greg Clarick, Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Matisyahu - business information, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Matisyahu - CD contract, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Matisyahu - CD design, Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Matisyahu - children's drawings, Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Matisyahu - commission statements, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Matisyahu - completed contracts, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Matisyahu - consignment records, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Matisyahu cover - Jewish Museum agreement, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Matisyahu - distribution contract, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Matisyahu - documentary proposal, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Matisyahu - fan mail, Undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Matisyahu - general contracts, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Matisyahu - instrumentalist forms, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Matisyahu - Jimmy Kimmel Live - name sign, Undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Matisyahu - "King without a Crown" video shooting schedule, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Matisyahu - management, 2004-2006 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Matisyahu - record marketing, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Matisyahu - settlement agreement, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Matisyahu - "Shake off the Dust" intellectual property rights form, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Matisyahu - video treatments, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Matisyahu - "Youth" video shoot schedule, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Meeting notes, Undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Music Pro Insurance, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - New Israel Fund Benefit Concert - contract, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - New Israel Fund Benefit Concert - production, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Notes and fragments, Undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Organizational development, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Outreach / business help pamphlets, Undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Pardes concert in NYC, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Pardes - Memorial Concert for Ben Blutstein and Marla Bennett in Tel Aviv - paperwork, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Proposals and notes, Undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Purim - Balkan Beat Box at SOB's, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Rock, Paper, Scissors - Balkan Beat Box promotion agreement, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - "The Reality of the Virtual"- looking for Jewish leadership online, c. 2009 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - "Reboot" directory, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Reboot - "Grande Vanilla Latte with Cinnamon...", 2006 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Reboot - "OMG! How Generation Y is Redefining Faith in the iPod Era", 2005 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Rocks Off concert cruise, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Rooftop Roots - agreement, 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Rooftop Roots: A JDub Mixtape - contracts, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Ropeadope Music Entertainment LLC - executive summary, Undated (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Schma-Journal - article by Aaron Bisman, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - The Silent Movie Theatre Co. - screening and party, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Six Points Fellowship - artist evaluation, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Slingshot Day - participant bios, Undated (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Slivovitz and Soul - parties, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Slivovitz and Soul - show, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - South by Southwest (SXSW), 2007 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - South by Southwest (SXSW), 2009 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Speaking notes, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Strategic Planning materials, Undated (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Time Warner - "Slingshot Day" program, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Tribe Fest, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Unity Sessions II, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Unity Sessions at Celebrate Brooklyn, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Unity Sessions at Opaline, NYC, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Unity Sessions Proposal, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Work for Hire - blank contract, Undated (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Zachor guest book, Undated (Box 3, Folder 74)
- Series IV: Financial Material
  This series contains invoices, bills, and checks paid by, and to, JDub Records. It also contains JDub's budgets.
- Series V: Commercial Media
  Conditions Governing Access
  Commercial media is available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
  This series contains professionally produced audio compact discs. Series B contains the print and other paper items associated with the discs, which were removed for preservation housing purposes.
  - Subseries A: Media
    - 26 Blue Moons - "Follow Your Dreams", Undated (Box 11)
      General
      Format: CD
    - Abrahami, Fiona Nehama - "Random Excess", 2009 (Box 11)
    - Adonai and I, 2001 (Box 11)
    - After the Service - "Give it Up", 2009 (Box 11)
    - Agur, Lior - "Singing for Life", Undated (Box 11)
    - Alan Cohen Experience - "Eat the Peace", 2009 (Box 11)
    - Alan Cohen Experience - "Revolutions", 2007 (Box 11)
    - Albertstein, Chava - "Lemele", 2006 (Box 11)
    - Alef - "Emergency", 1990 (Box 11)
    - Alexander, Aaron - "Midrash Mish Mosh", 2004 (Box 11)
    - Amitai, Paul - "River of Shadows", 2005 (Box 11)
    - Among the Hidden - "On the 27th Day", 2004 (Box 11)
    - Areddy, Hadara Levin - "After the Storm", 2006 (Box 11)
    - Asaf Avidan & The Mojos - "Lucky Man", 2009 (Box 11)
    - Asthmatix, The - "Latke", 2011 (Box 11)
    - Avni, Fran - "Israel World Beat", 1998 (Box 11)
    - Balkan Beat Box - "BBB Single 1", 2005 (Box 11)
    - Balkan Beat Box - "Blue Eyed Black Boy" (2 copies), Undated (Box 11)
    - Balkan Beat Box - "Bonnnaroo", 2006 (Box 11)
    - Balkan Beat Box - "Bonnaroo Live" (3 copies), 2006 (Box 11)
    - Balkan Beat Box - "CD 6180", 2005 (Box 11)
    - Balkan Beat Box - "Digital Monkey" (3 copies), 2007 (Box 11)
    - Balkan Beat Box - "Essay Recordings AY CD 08", 2005 (Box 11)
    - Balkan Beat Box - "JD 003" (3 copies), 2005 (Box 11)
    - Balkan Beat Box - "Nu Made (Remixes)(2 copies), 2009 (Box 11)
    - Balkan Beat Box - "Nu Made (Remixes)" promo (3 copies), 2009 (Box 11)
    - Balkan Beat Box - "Nu-Made (Remixes & Videos)", 2008 (Box 11)
    - Balkan Beat Box - "Nu-Med" (3 copies), 2007 (Box 11)
    - Balkan Beat Box - "Nu-Med" promo (2 copies), Undated (Box 11)
    - Bamidbar, Undated (Box 11)
    - Bar, Matt - "Bible Raps" (2 copies), 2009 (Box 11)
    - Beat'Achon - "Soul Food", 1997 (Box 11)
    - Beasts of Eden, The - "End Times", Undated (Box 11)
    - Beautiful Girls, The - "We're Already Gone", 2006 (Box 11)
    - Ben - "Noble Station", Undated (Box 11)
    - Benami, Channan - "The Wisdom of a Dream", 2010 (Box 11)
    - Benevento Russo Duo, The - "Best Reason to Buy the Sun", 2004 (Box 11)
    - Benlavain - "Come on People", 2005 (Box 11)
    - Bentor, Noa - "Waiting on a Shelf", 2005 (Box 11)
    - Beyond Eden - "On the D", 2004 (Box 11)
    - Biblical Digital, 2003 (Box 11)
    - Bigman, Nathan - "A Day Without a Funeral", 2005 (Box 11)
    - Bijou - "Where the Pavement Ends", 2006 (Box 11)
    - Bike Week 2007, Daytona Beach, Florida; Outer Banks, North Carolina (Box 11)
    - Bloom, Mark - "Holidays in Bloom" (2 Discs), 2009 (Box 11)
    - Blue Fringe - "70 Faces", 2005 (Box 11)
    - Bolton, Tuvia, Undated (Box 11)
    - Boogie Balagan - "Lamentation Walloo", Undated (Box 11)
    - Boom Pam, 2006 (Box 11)
    - Brian Bender and Little Shop of Horas - "Eyn Velt", 2008 (Box 11)
    - Brill, Wally - "The Covenant", 1997 (Box 11)
    - Brinks, Kodiak - "Stand for Nothing Fall for Anything", 2005 (Box 11)
    - Broussard, Marc - "Carencro", 2004 (Box 11)
    - Buccaneer - "Madly in Dub", 2010 (Box 11)
    - Burson, Clare - "Silver and Ash", 2009 (Box 11)
    - Burson, Clare - "Silver and Ash" sampler (3 copies), Undated (Box 11)
    - Burson, Clare - "Undone", 2001 (Box 11)
    - Cale, John - "Hobo Sapiens", 2003 (Box 11)
    - Carlebach, Neshama - "Ani Shelach", Undated (Box 11)
    - Carlebach, Neshama - "Journey", Undated (Box 11)
    - Carlebach, Neshama and Shlomo - "Ha Neshama Shel Shlomo", 1997 (Box 11)
    - Campbell, Yisrael - "...it's not in Heaven", 2005 (Box 11)
    - Celebrate Hip Hop, 2004 (Box 11)
    - Chaki, Adam - "Snowcité" (2 copies), 2006 (Box 11)
    - Chaki, Adam - "No One Knows Where The Hell We Are", 2001 (Box 11)
    - Chassidic Jazz Project, The, 2003 (Box 11)
    - Cheleman - "Como Duele La Verdad", 2005 (Box 11)
    - Chertman, Lila, 2008 (Box 11)
    - Chertman, Lila - "Every Soul", 2007 (Box 11)
    - Chimp Beams - "Menina", 2007 (Box 11)
    - Clarks, The - "Let it Go", 2000 (Box 11)
    - Cohen, Avishai - "After the Big Rain", Undated (Box 11)
    - Cohen, Mark & The Spirits - "Moments of Grace", 2005 (Box 11)
    - Collapsible Mammals, The, Undated (Box 11)
    - Compendium of All Things Close to Home:..., 2007 (Box 11)
    - Cool and Deadly, The, 2006 (Box 11)
    - Coolooloosh, 2004 (Box 11)
    - Coolooloosh - "Fight Rebel Sin", Undated (Box 11)
    - Cornerstone Player, The - no. 72 (3 copies), 2007 (Box 11)
    - Current TV - "Hanukah Shows", 2006 (Box 11)
    - Dam - "Dedication" (2 copies), 2006 (Box 11)
    - Dam - "Dedication" EPK, Undated (Box 11)
    - David, Joshua - "Visions of Hope", 2006 (Box 11)
    - Davka - "Live", 2005 (Box 11)
    - DeLeon - "Casata" (2 copies), 2011 (Box 11)
    - DeLeon - "Casata" promo (2 copies), 2011 (Box 11)
    - DeLeon - "DeLeon" (2 copies), 2008 (Box 11)
    - DeLeon - "DeLeon" promo (2 copies), 2008 (Box 11)
    - De Loco, Undated (Box 11)
    - Doctor D. - "Time on My Hands", 2006 (Box 11)
    - Double B - "And then everything got all awkward and I had to take her home", 2007 (Box 11)
    - Dramas, The - "The Actual Truth", Undated (Box 11)
    - DRK - "Cathartic Resume", 2005 (Box 11)
    - Duplaix, Vikter - "Bold and Beautiful", 2006 (Box 11)
    - Dubekot, Antje - "Big Dream Boulevard", 2006 (Box 11)
    - Eclectic Collective, The - "Time Flies", 2006 (Box 11)
    - Eden Mi Qedem, 2006 (Box 11)
    - Eilat, Yoni - "Tzigayner Neshume", 2010 (Box 12)
    - Eliaz, Ofri - "Ya Salio de la Mar", 2004 (Box 12)
    - Eliyahu, Mark - "Voices of Judea", 2005 (Box 12)
    - Emunah, Undated (Box 12)
    - Ennjin, Feersum, 2004 (Box 12)